

About Me

"I am a dynamic professional with experience in the IT field, from small to large companies. I have extensive experience in managing technical procedures and user support. I guarantee first, second and third level technical support. And with Solid knowledge in Operating Systems or with software creation for local automation, thus gaining agility."

Contact

+55 15 9 8833 2396 gustavogomes763@gmail.com Sorocaba-SP/Brazil

Skills

- Frameworks (ITIL e COBIT)
- Windows Server
- Structured Cabling
- Router and Switch Configurations
- OS Linux, Windows and macOS
- Information Security
- Cisco (Cisco PKT Tracer only)

Languages

- IntermediateEnglish
- Native
- Portuguese

BasicSpanish

GUSTAVO GOMES

IT Governance Analyst

Experience

IT2B - Technology | February 2020 - Present | IT Technician

"Serving the employees of the SP Court of Justice, solving problems in computer and judicial systems, Printers, Shared folders, Email configuration, among other requests."

Manchester Commercial Automation | August 2019 - January 2020

IT Technician

"Supporting users remotely or performing lab repairs; Repairing equipment (PC, Printers, and biometric clocks); Budgeting for customers; Assisting users in how to use the company's software and supporting them in making corrections to it."

Techlan | July 2016 - December 2016

IT Technician

"Supporting users, creating users through the company's Windows Server. Realization of dedicated Internet monitoring. Installation of Network Points of Certifications of the same. Maintenance and support of Printers. Budgeting of Services."

Education

Senac Brazil | Concluded in 2015

Technician in Computer Networks, System Networks and Telecommunications.

City University of São Paulo UNICID | Concluded in 2022

I.T. Management and Governance and Systems Analysis.